NATANAEL JEREMY KATIANDAGHO

Denpasar, Bali • 082339517855 • natanaeljeremy8@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/natanaeljeremyk

ABOUT

A proficient social media specalist with a track record of conceptualizing and aggressively implementing marketing to drive brand visibility and growth. Experienced in managing both a personal brand and an official online retail store. Highly skilled in communication and teamwork to deliver compelling business value to key stakeholders and clients.

EDUCATION

Universitas Merdeka Malang

Marketing Management GPA 3.89/4.00

September 2019 - September 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Udin Kashiwagi

July 2022 - July 2023

Content Creator

- Produced 59 video-based content for social media based on the latest social media trends; gained 3,942 Instagram followers, 5,850 YouTube subscribers, and 226,800 followers on TikTok in 1 month.
- Managed interaction with the followers on social media such as TikTok, Instagram, YouTube; gained 124.5K comments in 1 month.
- Conducted social media impact measurement and made informed decisions to accelerate performance; increased overall watch views by 212.45% to 36.8M views in 1 month..
- Created, developed, and executed a plan for social media strategies monthly (TikTok, Twitter, Instagram, and YouTube Short).

Delice Charme Indonesia

July 2023 – September 2023

Social Media Specialist

- Produced 70 video-based content for TikTok based on the latest social media trends; gained 584 followers in 1 month (July 2023 August 2023).
- Conducted social media impact measurement and made informed decision to accelerate performance; increased overall watch views by 75.5% to 69K views in 1 month.
- Sold IDR 8.1M gross revenue on TikTok Shop.
- Created, developed, and executed a plan for social media strategies monthly (TikTok).

COURSE

Digital Marketing

Google Digital Garage March 2023

• The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Digital Marketing

RevoU April 2023

• *Intro to Digital Marketing*

Creative Copywriting

MySkill May 2023

• Creative Copywriting

Social Media Marketing

eMarketing Institute July 2022

• *eMarketing Institute Social Media Marketing*

English

EF English First July 2022

• EF Standard English Test (EF SET) (C1 Advanced)

SKILLS & OTHER: Marketing, Public Speaking, Video Producing, Storytelling, Copywriting, TikTok Ads **LANGUAGE:** English (*C1 Advanced*), Indonesian (*Native*)